missoma.com 2016-11-19

# Missoma

PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED

## PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED

We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and secondly, to provide you with the best possible service. We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent. Missoma only collects information when you volunteer it when registering your details for online payment – you have the option to refuse any future marketing emails from us.

_The type of information we will collect about you includes:  _  
* Your Name * Address * Delivery Address * Phone Number * E-mail Address   
(Collectively ‘Your Personal Data’).

## RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We take appropriate measures to ensure that any personal data is kept secure and is kept for only so long as is necessary for the purpose for which it is used.  
If your personal details change or if you have any queries about how we use your Personal Data, please notify missoma.com by emailing our Customer Service Team at [_shop@missoma.com_](mailto:shop@missoma.com).

## AUTOMATICALLY RECORDED INFORMATION 

When you access the Missoma website, general non-personal information (Internet browser used, number of visits, average time spent on site, pages viewed) is recorded automatically (not as part of website maintenance). This information is used to gauge our website's appeal and to improve its content and functionality. Your data is not processed any further nor is it transmitted to any third parties.

## Cookies

We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a cookie internet file, a small file that is sent by our web server to your computer, which we can access when you make return visits to our Website. Storing cookies is usual practice for any website that needs to remember what its users’ preferences are and we use cookies to keep track of your selections on the Website. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening ([ _www.aboutcookies.org_](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for more information on this). If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features on our website, including the ability to purchase items.

## Security Policy

To process an order we need your credit / debit card number and expiry date, plus any security details that the credit card processor may require. Missoma employs trusted and reputable third party hosting agents and payment providers to ensure the security of personal data. All credit card details that are given to us by you the customer are done so on a secure server using Sage Pay. The transfer of the purchase details from our site to Sage Pay are encapsulated using their encrypted and digitally-signed protocol. This uses a combination of standard methods to ensure that the information passed is secure and tamper-proof. Sage Pay is level 1 (the highest level) PCI DSS compliant and is regulated by qualified security assessor Trustwave. Please note, we do not store any financial information from you.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any material changes we may make to our Privacy Policy will be updated in our Privacy Policy section. Please review it occasionally to remain informed and updated.

How we use your personal data

RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

AUTOMATICALLY RECORDED INFORMATION 

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

## PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED

We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and secondly, to provide you with the best possible service. We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent. Missoma only collects information when you volunteer it when registering your details for online payment – you have the option to refuse any future marketing emails from us.

_The type of information we will collect about you includes:  _  
* Your Name * Address * Delivery Address * Phone Number * E-mail Address   
(Collectively ‘Your Personal Data’).

## How we use your personal data

We will use ‘Your Personal Data’ that you provide to us:  
To enable us to provide the services relevant to you  
To alert you to any product and service changes and updated information  
For administration and marketing purposes.  

In the event you do not wish for us to use ‘Your Personal Data’ for administration and marketing purposes, please either:  
Click on the ‘Unsubscribe’ link in the emails we have sent you (if any); or contact our Customer Service Team by emailing [_shop@missoma.com_](mailto:shop@missoma.com) and advising us of your intention to be removed from our marketing database.  
We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by e-mailing us at [_shop@missoma.com_](mailto:shop@missoma.com). If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly. The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. Missoma will neither sell your personal data to third parties nor market it elsewhere. The employees of Missoma are duty-bound to respect the confidentiality of your data and abide by the UK’s Jewellery Retail Codes of Conduct.  

## RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We take appropriate measures to ensure that any personal data is kept secure and is kept for only so long as is necessary for the purpose for which it is used.  
If your personal details change or if you have any queries about how we use your Personal Data, please notify missoma.com by emailing our Customer Service Team at [_shop@missoma.com_](mailto:shop@missoma.com).

## AUTOMATICALLY RECORDED INFORMATION 

When you access the Missoma website, general non-personal information (Internet browser used, number of visits, average time spent on site, pages viewed) is recorded automatically (not as part of website maintenance). This information is used to gauge our website's appeal and to improve its content and functionality. Your data is not processed any further nor is it transmitted to any third parties.

## Cookies

We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a cookie internet file, a small file that is sent by our web server to your computer, which we can access when you make return visits to our Website. Storing cookies is usual practice for any website that needs to remember what its users’ preferences are and we use cookies to keep track of your selections on the Website. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening ([ _www.aboutcookies.org_](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for more information on this). If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features on our website, including the ability to purchase items.

## Security Policy

To process an order we need your credit / debit card number and expiry date, plus any security details that the credit card processor may require. Missoma employs trusted and reputable third party hosting agents and payment providers to ensure the security of personal data. All credit card details that are given to us by you the customer are done so on a secure server using Sage Pay. The transfer of the purchase details from our site to Sage Pay are encapsulated using their encrypted and digitally-signed protocol. This uses a combination of standard methods to ensure that the information passed is secure and tamper-proof. Sage Pay is level 1 (the highest level) PCI DSS compliant and is regulated by qualified security assessor Trustwave. Please note, we do not store any financial information from you.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any material changes we may make to our Privacy Policy will be updated in our Privacy Policy section. Please review it occasionally to remain informed and updated.
